[
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous group performed the first ever song on Top Of The Pops in 1964?",
        "Answer": "The Rolling Stones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band has released albums titled Word Gets Around, Just Enough Education To Perform and Pull The Pin?",
        "Answer": "Stereophonics"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which supermodel is seen pole dancing in the White Stripes video for the song I Just Don't Know What To Do With Myself?",
        "Answer": "Kate Moss"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatle led the way across the zebra crossing on the Abbey Road album cover?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which world famous musician was born Farrokh Bulsara in Zanzibar in 1946?",
        "Answer": "Freddie Mercury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group formed in 1977 and named themselves after their financial status at that time?",
        "Answer": "Dire Straits"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Bob the Builder's second UK number one hit single?",
        "Answer": "Mambo No 5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which supermaket is mentioned in Chas and Dave's song Rabbit?",
        "Answer": "Sainsbury's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer had hits with Rubber Ball and The Night Has A Thousand Eyes?",
        "Answer": "Bobby Vee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which country did Celine Dion represent when singing in the Eurovision Song Contest in 1988?",
        "Answer": "Switzerland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What group with a palindromic name had a hit single that was also a palindrome?",
        "Answer": "ABBA (with SOS)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which artist released an album and movie under the same title of Get Rich Or Die Tryin'?",
        "Answer": "50 Cent"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which US rapper died on September 13th 1996 after being shot in a drive-by shooting after watchin Mike Tysons comeback fight 7 days earlier?",
        "Answer": "Tupac Shakur"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the Sinead O'Connor hit Nothing Compares 2 U?",
        "Answer": "Prince"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop singer did Debbie Rowe marry?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The pop groups Ace Of Base and The Cardigans both hail from which country?",
        "Answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In musical notes, which is bigger - a crotchet or a semibreve?",
        "Answer": "Semibreve"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British female singer had a 2006 hit with 'Rehab'?",
        "Answer": "Amy Winehouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Barbadian singer stayed ten weeks at number 1 with 'Umbrella'?",
        "Answer": "Rihanna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was Mozart?",
        "Answer": "Austrian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer had a string of hits in the 1970s and is often referred to as the 'Queen of Disco'?",
        "Answer": "Donna Summer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which boy's name was the title of the debut album released by Amy Winehouse?",
        "Answer": "Frank"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a number one album in 1979 with Regatta De Blanc?",
        "Answer": "The Police"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit single in 1964 with 'Little Red Rooster'?",
        "Answer": "The Rolling Stones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1963, which band became the first to reach number one with their first three singles?",
        "Answer": "Gerry and the Pacemakers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is Schubert's Symphony No. 8 better known?",
        "Answer": "Unfinished Symphony"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is singer Pauline Matthews better known?",
        "Answer": "Kiki Dee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common link between The Dave Clark 5, Fat Larry's Band and Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes?",
        "Answer": "All three are named after their drummer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "George Bernard Shaw's play 'Pygmalion' was adapted to become which musical?",
        "Answer": "My Fair Lady"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had hits with 'Linger' and 'Dreams'?",
        "Answer": "The Cranberries"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the double act of David Peacock and Charles Hodges better known?",
        "Answer": "Chas 'n' Dave"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, which band consists of Billy Gibbons, Dusty Hill and Frank Beard?",
        "Answer": "ZZ Top"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Formed in 1976, which famous band consists of Paul Hewson, Dave Evans, Adam Clayton and Larry Mullen, Jr?",
        "Answer": "U2 (Paul Hewson is 'Bono', Dave Evans is 'The Edge')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which well known band was formed in 1973 by brothers Angus and Malcolm Young?",
        "Answer": "AC/DC"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Billy J. Kramer's backing group in the 1960s?",
        "Answer": "The Dakotas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit with 'La Bamba' in 1987?",
        "Answer": "Los Lobos"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single in 1981 with 'Romeo And Juliet'?",
        "Answer": "Dire Straits"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single in 1974 with 'The Streak'?",
        "Answer": "Ray Stevens"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop band had a hit single with 'Open Your Heart' in 1981?",
        "Answer": "The Human League"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1985 with 'One More Night'?",
        "Answer": "Phil Collins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1982 with 'Maneater'?",
        "Answer": "Hall And Oates"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a hit with 'He Ain't Heavy, He's My Brother' in both 1969 and 1988?",
        "Answer": "The Hollies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single with 'Crocodile Rock' in 1972?",
        "Answer": "Elton John"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single in 1961 with 'Runaway'?",
        "Answer": "Del Shannon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1985 with 'One More Night'?",
        "Answer": "Phil Collins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the lead singer of The Four Seasons in the 1960s and 1970s?",
        "Answer": "Frankie Valli"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit with '24 Hours From Tulsa' in 1963?",
        "Answer": "Gene Pitney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit with a cover version of Frankie Laine's hit single 'I Believe' in 1996?",
        "Answer": "Robson And Jerome"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a hit with 'Too Shy' in 1983?",
        "Answer": "Kajagoogoo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Zager and Evans hit single of 1969 had the words Exordium and Terminus in brackets in the title?",
        "Answer": "In the year 2525"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous comedian made a record called 'please mister custer' in 1960?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Drake"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980 Splodgenessabounds hit gives its name to the title of a BBC comedy series?",
        "Answer": "Two Pints of Lager and a Packet of Crisps, Please!"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first song played on Radio One on 30 September 1967?",
        "Answer": "'Flowers in the Rain' by the Move"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a hit record in the 1970s, the 1980s and the 1990s and each time they had a completely different line up?",
        "Answer": "The England World Cup Squad"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which instrument was Dizzy Gillespie famous for playing?",
        "Answer": "The trumpet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang lead vocals on Australian group Python Lee Jackson's  1972 hit 'In a broken dream'?",
        "Answer": "Rod Stewart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer won the Eurovision Song Contest for Ireland in 1980 and 1987?",
        "Answer": "Johnny Logan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the clockwork device used by musicians to measure time?",
        "Answer": "Metronome"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The song 'Killing Me Softly With His Song' was written about which American singer-songwriter?",
        "Answer": "Don McLean"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Culture Club's first number one in the UK?",
        "Answer": "Do You Really Want To Hurt Me?"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous pop star was christened Charles Westover?",
        "Answer": "Del Shannon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The town of Titipu in Japan, the Tower of London and Venice in Italy. What is the musical connection?",
        "Answer": "They're all settings for Gilbert and Sullivan operas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop band named itself after an American firetruck?",
        "Answer": "REO Speedwagon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The original Live Aid concerts were held at Wembly and Philadelphia on 13th July in which year?",
        "Answer": "1985"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whay song did Whitney Houston record for the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics?",
        "Answer": "One Moment In Time"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the first line of the USA for Africa's 'We Are The World'?",
        "Answer": "Lionel Richie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Flowers In The Rain' holds the distinction of being the very first record played on Radio One, but who performed it?",
        "Answer": "The Move"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American soul singer's dad played football for Glasgow Celtic ?",
        "Answer": "Gil Scott-Heron"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Paul released his first single 'I Confess' when he was 14 and had written over 200 songs by the time he was 21?",
        "Answer": "Paul Anka"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the common title of 3 different songs released by 3 different artists that all entered the Top 20 UK charts in 1985?",
        "Answer": "'The Power Of Love' (by Huey Lewis and the News, Frankie Goes To Hollywood and Jennifer Rush)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Elvis Presley's first British number 1?",
        "Answer": "All Shook Up"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which artist has had number one singles in the UK as a solo artist, as part of a duo, as part of a  trio, as part of a quartet and as part of a group with more than four members?",
        "Answer": "Sir Paul McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Alex Band and Aaron Kamin make up which band?",
        "Answer": "The Calling"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is singer Paul Hewson better known?",
        "Answer": "Bono"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1976, which single was knocked from the number one spot by a single whose title was contained in the lyrics to the first single?",
        "Answer": "Bohemian Rhapsody by Queen (being replaced by Mamma Mia by Abba)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the theme tune to the film 'The Neverending Story'?",
        "Answer": "Limahl"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Elvis Presley die?",
        "Answer": "1977"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was lead singer for 70s glam rock band 'The Sweet'?",
        "Answer": "Brian Connelly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'No Sleep Till Brooklyn' was a hit single for which group in 1987?",
        "Answer": "Beastie Boys"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Justin Timberlake was formerly a vocalist for which band?",
        "Answer": "N Sync"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band a 70s hit with 'Son of my father'?",
        "Answer": "Chicory Tip"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band does Rocky Gray play the drums for?",
        "Answer": "Evanescence"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the original name of Cliff Richard's backing group 'The Shadows' before they realised there was already an American group with the same name?",
        "Answer": "The Drifters"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a 1983 hit with 'Too Shy'?",
        "Answer": "Kajagoogoo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which real-life Russian did Boney M sing about in 1978?",
        "Answer": "Rasputin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As of September 2005 there are two albums from the 1990s that are in the top ten albums of all time and both are by solo female artists. Who are they?",
        "Answer": "Whitney Houston and Shania Twain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1984 with '99 Red Balloons'?",
        "Answer": "Nena"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which world famous star is a member of the band '30 odd foot of grunts'?",
        "Answer": "Russel Crowe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Iron Maidens mascot who appears on their album covers and who has also featured in a video game?",
        "Answer": "Eddie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which heavy metal band had a UK number hit in January 1991 and what was the name of the song?",
        "Answer": "Iron Maiden with 'Bring Your Daughter To The Slaughter'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single with 'Werewolves Of London'?",
        "Answer": "Warren Zevon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many number 1 singles did Kim Wilde and her dad Marty have between them?",
        "Answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many grooves are on one side of an LP record?",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980s pop star's autobiography is entitled 'Take It Like A Man'?",
        "Answer": "Boy George (George O'Dowd)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the music and lyrics to the musical 'Anything Goes'?",
        "Answer": "Cole Porter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Paul McCartney's middle name?",
        "Answer": "Paul"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many times are the words 'Hey Jude' mentioned in the Beatles song of the same name? 14, 24 or 34?",
        "Answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do the songs 'Killer' by Adamski, 'Paranoid Android' by Radiohead and 'True Faith' by New Order have in common?",
        "Answer": "The song titles aren't mentioned in the lyrics"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For what is Michael Eavis best known in the music world?",
        "Answer": "The Glastonbury Festival"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which popstar was actor Emilio Estevez formerly married to?",
        "Answer": "Paula Abdul"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How old was Elvis Presley when he had his first number one single?",
        "Answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which UK group were banned from entering the U.S. for unspecified reasons from 1965 to 1969?",
        "Answer": "The Kinks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, how was Jiles Perry Richardson better known?",
        "Answer": "The Big Bopper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous rock group played their first gig together at the Marquee Club in London on July 12th, 1962?",
        "Answer": "The Rolling Stones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which record label did Sam Phillips sell Elvis Presley to in 1955?",
        "Answer": "R.C.A."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is credited as having discovered the singer Kate Bush?",
        "Answer": "Dave Gilmour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many grooves does an average vinyl long playing record have?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the lead singer in The Police?",
        "Answer": "Sting"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Now better known as an actress, who was Britains entry in the Eurovision Song Contest in 1991 with the song 'A Message To Your Heart'?",
        "Answer": "Samantha Janus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the theme for the Bond film 'From Russia With Love'?",
        "Answer": "Matt Monroe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first member to leave Guns 'N' Roses",
        "Answer": "Steve Adler"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang with KLF on their 1991 hit single 'Justified And Ancient'?",
        "Answer": "Tammy Wynette"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Britains entry in the Eurovision Song Contest in 1964 with the song 'I Love The Little Things'?",
        "Answer": "Matt Monroe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Britains entry in the Eurovision Song Contest in 1968 with the song 'Congratulations'?",
        "Answer": "Cliff Richard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released the 1983 album 'Sports'?",
        "Answer": "Huey Lewis and the News"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop group had their first number one in the UK with a cover version of A-Ha's 'Take On Me'?",
        "Answer": "A1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group formed in Oxford in the late 1980s and took their name from a song by Talking Heads?",
        "Answer": "Radiohead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Spice Girl realeased the album 'Schizophonic'?",
        "Answer": "Geri Halliwell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the song 'The Twelve Days Of Christmas', how what did my true love give to me on the 12th day?",
        "Answer": "12 Drummers Drumming"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hits in the seventies with 'Everybody Dance' and 'Good Times'?",
        "Answer": "Chic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hits in the seventies with 'Everybody Dance' and 'Good Times'?",
        "Answer": "Chic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won a Grammy in 2002 for her vocal on the song 'I'm Like A Bird'?",
        "Answer": "Nelly Furtardo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which band is Fred Durst the lead singer?",
        "Answer": "Limp Bizkit"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The lyrics 'There are many things that I would like to say to you, but I don't know how' come from which 1990s song?",
        "Answer": "'Wonderwall' (by Oasis)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which month of the year do crowds visit Graceland to honour Elvis on the anniversary of his death?",
        "Answer": "August"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many black keys are there on the a standard piano?",
        "Answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at May 2001, what is Pink Floyd's only UK number one single?",
        "Answer": "'Another Brick In The Wall'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female pop-star's debut album was called 'Honey to the B'?",
        "Answer": "Billie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the song 'Rhapsody In Blue'?",
        "Answer": "George Gershwin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor turned singer was born James Michael Aloysius Bradford in 1954?",
        "Answer": "Jimmy Nail"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hits in the sixties including 'Something's Happening', 'Silhouettes' and 'I'm Into Something Good'?",
        "Answer": "Herman's Hermits"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose first solo number one was called 'Forever Love' in 1996?",
        "Answer": "Gary Barlow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the christmas song 'Driving Home For Christmas'?",
        "Answer": "Chris Rea"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which 1968 film did the band Duran Duran get their name?",
        "Answer": "Barbarella"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Soul singer, Bobby Brown, married which successful female singer in 1992?",
        "Answer": "Whitney Houston"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1975 with 'I'm Not In Love'?",
        "Answer": "10cc"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who recorded the 1994 album 'Return Of The Space Cowboy'?",
        "Answer": "Jamiroquai"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Lightning Seeds song includes the line 'Oh you fool, you've got me started'?",
        "Answer": "Change"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Les McKeown was the lead singer with which Scottish pop group?",
        "Answer": "The Bay City Rollers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the title track for the Bond Film 'For Your Eyes Only'?",
        "Answer": "Sheena Easton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Dutch duo of Ray Slijngaard and Anita Dels, who had 8 top ten hits in the 90s, were better known by what name?",
        "Answer": "2 Unlimited"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which solo artist had the second and third best-selling albums of the 1980s in the UK?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Pulp's first top ten hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Common People'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What group released the album 'Voodoo Lounge' in 1994?",
        "Answer": "The Rolling Stones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which groups first UK top ten hit was 'Follow You, Follow Me' in 1978?",
        "Answer": "Genesis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer's original name was Elizabeth Bookbinder?",
        "Answer": "Elkie Brooks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Actors from which TV soap opera had a hit with the song 'Hillbilly Rock'?",
        "Answer": "Emmerdale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Roisin Murphy is the singer in which band?",
        "Answer": "Moloko"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What instrument was Louis Armstrong most famous for playing?",
        "Answer": "The trumpet."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a Christmas number one in 1974 with 'Lonely This Christmas'?",
        "Answer": "Mud"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2002, who was the only musician to be voted in the top ten in BBC's 'Great Briton's' poll?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the local farmer who organises the Glastonbury music festival?",
        "Answer": "Michael Eavis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor had a top ten hit called 'Mona' in 1990?",
        "Answer": "Craig McLachlan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the surnames of the three tenors?",
        "Answer": "Pavarotti, Carraras, Domingo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit with 'The Israelites' in 1969?",
        "Answer": "Desmond Dekker and the Aces"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Joe Strummer was the lead singer with which famous British band?",
        "Answer": "The Clash"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Def Leppard's first UK top ten hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Animal'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the Spice Girls' debut single called?",
        "Answer": "'Wannabee'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Released in 1978, what was the title of Kate Bush's second album? Braveheart, Lionheart or Sweetheart?",
        "Answer": "Lionheart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had their first UK number one in 1999 with 'I Want It That Way'?",
        "Answer": "Backstreet Boys"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the opera 'The Magic Flute'?",
        "Answer": "Mozart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the biggest selling single in the UK in the 1980s?",
        "Answer": "'Do They Know Its Christmas' by Band Aid"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which instrument was Benny Goodman famous for playing?",
        "Answer": "Clarinet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the villain Howard Payne in the film 'Speed'?",
        "Answer": "Dennis Hopper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of country music's first superstar who died at the age of 29 from drink and drug abuse?",
        "Answer": "Hank Williams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Billy Ocean's first number one single?",
        "Answer": "'Caribbean Queen'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band were accused of poll rigging in 1999, when they won the Brit award for best newcomer?",
        "Answer": "Belle & Sebastian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band member is missing from the line-up Ray Manzarek, Robby Krieger and John Densmore?",
        "Answer": "Jim Morrisson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the lead singer with the band Thin Lizzy?",
        "Answer": "Phil Lynott"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was known as the 'First Lady of Country Music'?",
        "Answer": "Tammy Wynette"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who released her debut album 'Can't Take Me Home' in 2000?",
        "Answer": "Pink"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2003, who won the Best Male Solo Artist award at the Brits?",
        "Answer": "Robbie Williams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the 90s song which includes the line 'I swear I left her by the river'?",
        "Answer": "Hazard (by Richard Marx)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a UK number 2 hit in 1967 with 'Hole In My Shoe', which was covered in 1985 by Neil from the TV show 'The Young Ones'?",
        "Answer": "Traffic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Olly Peacock is the drummer with which group?",
        "Answer": "Gomez"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which city was singer Craig David born in?",
        "Answer": "Southampton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American state is the museum called the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?",
        "Answer": "Ohio"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which US three piece band is made up of Taylor, Isaac and Zac?",
        "Answer": "Hanson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous singer was born David Jones in 1947?",
        "Answer": "David Bowie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Thom Yorke is the lead singer with which band?",
        "Answer": "Radiohead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Sonia's number one hit single of 1989?",
        "Answer": "'You'll Never Stop Me Loving You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The soundtrack to which film was the best selling album in the UK in 1992?",
        "Answer": "'The Bodyguard'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American rock band had a UK top ten hit single in 1987 with 'Alone'?",
        "Answer": "Heart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Mark Snow had a hit single in 1996 with the theme from which TV series?",
        "Answer": "The X-Files"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following operas was not composed by Puccini? Madame Butterfly, Tosca or The Barber Of Seville?",
        "Answer": "The Barber Of Seville"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a top ten hit in 1987 called 'Shattered Dreams'?",
        "Answer": "Johnny Hates Jazz"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a 2001 hit with a cover version of Billy JoelÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s 'Uptown Girl'?",
        "Answer": "Westlife"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which group would you most associate singer Bobby Gillespie?",
        "Answer": "Primal Scream"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which R.E.M. song includes the line 'Let's play twister, let's play risk'?",
        "Answer": "Man On The Moon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Pet Shop Boys had a UK Christmas Number 1 in 1987 with a song that was co-written by country star, Willie Nelson. What was the name of the song?",
        "Answer": "'Always On My Mind'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Whitney Houston's first UK number one hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Saving All My Love For You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Bob Marley's backing band called?",
        "Answer": "The Whalers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band's first top ten single was 'Love Is Life' in 1970?",
        "Answer": "Hot Chocolate"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who's 1978 debut single was called 'Sultans Of Swing'?",
        "Answer": "Dire Straits"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played bass guitar in the Beatles?",
        "Answer": "Paul McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which decade did the Eurovision Song contest begin?",
        "Answer": "1950s (1956)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a top ten hit in May 1990 with 'I Still Haven't Found What I'm Looking For'?",
        "Answer": "The Chimes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of Michael Jackson's albums sold most copies in the UK? 'Thriller' or 'Bad'?",
        "Answer": "'Bad'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Bucks Fizz win the European Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "1981"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous singer-songwriter won an Academy Award in 2001 for the song 'Things Have Changed' from the film 'Wonder Boys'?",
        "Answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which rock star did Joan Rivers describe as being 'the only man with child-bearing lips'?",
        "Answer": "Mick Jagger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 90's song includes the line 'Take a deep breath and get real high' and who had a hit with it?",
        "Answer": "'What's Up' by Four Non-Blondes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who has had albums called 'Blonde On Blonde', 'Blood On The Tracks' and 'Highway 61 Revisited'?",
        "Answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Michael Ball's song for Britain in the 1992 Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "One Step Out Of Time"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group sang the song 'Take My Breath Away' which featured in the film 'Top Gun'?",
        "Answer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of the Sex Pistol's first British hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Anarchy in the UK'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What brand of beer does Homer Simpson drink?",
        "Answer": "Duff"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female vocalist released the album 'Drag'?",
        "Answer": "K. D. Lang"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the first ventriloquist's dummy to have a top ten hit in the UK charts?",
        "Answer": "Orville"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Nicole won the Eurovision Song Contest for which country in 1982?",
        "Answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, which is the lowest male voice?",
        "Answer": "Bass"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city is the record company Motown based?",
        "Answer": "Detroit"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song won the best British single awards at the Brits in February 2002?",
        "Answer": "'Don't Stop Moving' (by S Club 7)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song includes the line 'She'll make you take your clothes off and go dancing in the rain'?",
        "Answer": "'Livin' La Vie Da Loca' (by Ricky Martin)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had a top ten hit with 'Another Suitcase In Another Hall' in 1997?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Cliff Richard single was at number one over Christmas in the UK in 1988?",
        "Answer": "'Mistletoe and Wine'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit with 'Tiger Feet' in 1974?",
        "Answer": "Mud"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Cliff Richard's real name?",
        "Answer": "Harry Webb"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which ice cream has been advertised on TV to the tune of 'It's Now Or Never'?",
        "Answer": "Cornetto"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatles song was a number one for 'Ferry Aid'?",
        "Answer": "'Let It Be'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the Pet Shop Boys' first hit single?",
        "Answer": "West End Girls"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedy duo had a number one hit with 'The Stonk' in 1991?",
        "Answer": "Hale and Pace"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many bottles were washed up on the shore according to the rock band, the Police ?",
        "Answer": "One hundred million"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a top ten hit in 1983 called 'Rip It Up'?",
        "Answer": "Orange Juice"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Scandanavian pop group Aqua had a hit single about which doctor?",
        "Answer": "'Dr Jones'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which football team do Liam and Noel Gallagher of Oasis support?",
        "Answer": "Manchester City"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop group comprised Vince Clarke and Alison Moyet?",
        "Answer": "Yazoo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the female singer in the band Everything But The Girl?",
        "Answer": "Tracey Thorn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Top Of The Pops first shown?",
        "Answer": "1964"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Elton John's 'Candle in the Wind' originally written about?",
        "Answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1965, who became country music's first female millionaire?",
        "Answer": "Loretta Lynn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Alan White replaced Tony McCarroll as the drummer for which band?",
        "Answer": "Oasis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop group took its name from a character in the film 'Barbarella'?",
        "Answer": "Duran Duran"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Spice Girl had a number one single with 'I Turn To You'?",
        "Answer": "Melanie C"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What famous song did Francis Scott Key write in 1814?",
        "Answer": "The Star Spangled Banner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Guns N Roses song did the band Texas cover in 1992?",
        "Answer": "'Sweet Child O' Mine'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the Beatles officially split up?",
        "Answer": "1970"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Rossini composed an overture about what legendary character? William The Conqueror, William Tell or King Arthur?",
        "Answer": "William Tell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of the Spice Girls' debut album?",
        "Answer": "'Spice'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had top ten hits with 'Gangsters' and 'Nelson Mandela'?",
        "Answer": "The Specials"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had top ten hits with 'Gangsters' and 'Nelson Mandela'?",
        "Answer": "The Specials"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of The Who's drummer, who died in 1978?",
        "Answer": "Keith Moon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the word 'forte' mean in music? Soft, Fast or Loud?",
        "Answer": "Loud"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many strings does a ukulele have?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1983, what became the Eurythmics first UK top ten single?",
        "Answer": "'Sweet Dreams (Are Made Of This)'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following operas was first performed before the other two? The Magic Flute, Carmen or Fidelio?",
        "Answer": "The Magic Flute"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the opera 'Carmen'? Mozart, Purcell or Bizet?",
        "Answer": "Bizet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which instrument did Karen Carpenter play in The Carpenters before becoming lead singer?",
        "Answer": "Drums"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, how is Gordon Sumner better known?",
        "Answer": "Sting"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What famous heavy metal band is named after a medieval torture device?",
        "Answer": "Iron Maiden"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of No Doubt's hit single which included the line 'Don't tell me cos it hurts'?",
        "Answer": "Don't Speak"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is singer Dido's surname?",
        "Answer": "Armstrong"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a top 20 hit in 1993 called 'Everybody Dance'? Downtown, Evolution or Baby D?",
        "Answer": "Evolution"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a top ten hit with 'Waterfalls' in 1995?",
        "Answer": "TLC"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer received 6 nominations at the Brit Awards in 2001, but didn't win a single prize?",
        "Answer": "Craig David"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the Eurythmics first UK number one single?",
        "Answer": "'There Must Be An Angel (Playing With My Heart)'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Vincent Furnier is the real name of which rock star?",
        "Answer": "Alice Cooper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Simon and Garfunkel release their album 'Bridge Over Troubled Water'? 1970, 1973 or 1975?",
        "Answer": "1970"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, who has sometimes been called the 'thin white duke'?",
        "Answer": "David Bowie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What city in South Carolina gave its name to a popular dance in the early 20th century?",
        "Answer": "Charleston"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What musical gave Jason Donovan his first starring West End role?",
        "Answer": "'Joseph and his Amazing Technicolour Dreamcoat'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band made up the panel on the British TV show 'Juke Box Jury' on the only week the panel consisted of five people?",
        "Answer": "The Rolling Stones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatles album consisted only of Lennon and McCartney compositions?",
        "Answer": "'A Hard Day's Night'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang 'Anyone who had a heart' in 1964?",
        "Answer": "Cilla Black"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the ballet 'Sleeping Beauty'?",
        "Answer": "Tchaikovsky"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Oasis' 1994 debut single?",
        "Answer": "'Supersonic'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote 'Everytime You Go Away' which was a successful hit for Paul Young?",
        "Answer": "Daryll Hall"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How was 80's music star Stuard Goddard better known?",
        "Answer": "Adam Ant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Norwegian band had a hit with 'Manhattan Skyline'?",
        "Answer": "A-ha"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Elvis Presley buy Graceland? 1957, 1962 or 1968?",
        "Answer": "1957"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Chuck Berry's 1972 hit which gave him his first number one?",
        "Answer": "My Ding-A-Ling"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single in 2000 called 'Love Don't Cost A Thing'?",
        "Answer": "Jennifer Lopez"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had UK top ten singles with 'Jump',  and 'Why Can't This Be Love'?",
        "Answer": "Van Halen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Black Lace's song for Britain in the 1979 Eurovision Song Contest? 'Mary Ann', 'Beg, Steal or Borrow' or 'Ring-A-Ding Girl'?",
        "Answer": "Mary Ann"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "B.B. King guested with which band to record the song 'When Love Comes To Town'?",
        "Answer": "U2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Madonna's first top ten single?",
        "Answer": "'Holiday'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Bjork song includes the line 'He believes in beauty'?",
        "Answer": "Venus As A Boy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which successful British pop group got their name from part of the title of children's tv show and part of a song by Roxy Music?",
        "Answer": "Bananarama (from 'The Banana Splits' and 'Pyjamarama')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Does a record turntable revolve clockwise or anti-clockwise?",
        "Answer": "Clockwise"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of music originated in Seattle in the early 1990s and brought commercial success for Nirvana?",
        "Answer": "Grunge"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of music originated in Seattle in the early 1990s and brought commercial success for Nirvana?",
        "Answer": "Grunge"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose only UK top ten single is 'Oxygene (part IV)'?",
        "Answer": "Jean Michel Jarre"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the band All Saints' number one hit which was featured on the soundtrack to the film 'The Beach'?",
        "Answer": "'Pure Shores'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of George Gershwin's brother, who also wrote music?",
        "Answer": "Ira"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was the composer Handel?",
        "Answer": "German"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Scandanavian group had a top 20 hit in 1993 called 'Dark Is The Night'?",
        "Answer": "A-Ha"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one in 1960 called 'Only The Lonely'?",
        "Answer": "Roy Orbison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Dire Straits album was the bestselling album in the UK in the 1980s?",
        "Answer": "'Brothers In Arms'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer's 1985 autobiography was called 'Who's Sorry Now'?",
        "Answer": "Connie Francis'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had hits in the 80s with 'Harvest For The World' and 'Ideal World'?",
        "Answer": "The Christians"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In January 2000, which singer was found with 15.2 grams of marijuana at an airport in Hawaii?",
        "Answer": "Whitney Houston"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor had a number one hit in 1975 with the song 'If'?",
        "Answer": "Telly Savalas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Greg Lake's top ten Christmas hit of 1975?",
        "Answer": "I Believe In Father Christmas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American singer has a backing band called 'The E Street Band'?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Springsteen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer released the album 'Lionheart'?",
        "Answer": "Kate Bush"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the largest stringed instrument in a classical orchestra?",
        "Answer": "Double bass"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the music world how was Ray Burns better known?",
        "Answer": "Captain Sensible"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which hit from the glory days of rock and roll contains the lyrics 'When you left me all alone, at the record hop, told me you were going out for a soda pop'?",
        "Answer": "'Lipstick On Your Collar' (by Connie Francis)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the opera 'Madame Butterfly'?",
        "Answer": "Puccini"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a hit album in 1977 with 'Arrival'?",
        "Answer": "Abba"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which star from the world of music is the famous father of Paris Michael Katherine, born in 1998?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a number one hit in 2004 called 'Five Colours in Her Hair'?",
        "Answer": "McFly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Peter, Paul and Mary had a hit in 1963 with which Bob Dylan song?",
        "Answer": "Blowin' In The Wind"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Cliff Richards' first number one single?",
        "Answer": "'Living Doll'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had the bestselling album in the UK in 1998 called 'Falling Into You'?",
        "Answer": "Celine Dion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Def Leppard and Mud both had hit singles with what same name?",
        "Answer": "Rocket"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which all-male group spent more weeks on the UK charts in the 1980s than any other group?",
        "Answer": "Madness"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hit albums in the seventies with 'Low' and 'Lodger'?",
        "Answer": "David Bowie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who reached number 7 in the UK charts in 1972 with the single 'Layla'?",
        "Answer": "Derek And The Dominoes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer sang the James Bond theme song 'Goldeneye' and which two members of another band wrote it?",
        "Answer": "Tina Turner sang it, Bono and The Edge of U2 wrote it."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common title of hit singles by Holly Johnson and The O'Jays?",
        "Answer": "'Love Train'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released the 1987 album 'Appetite For Destruction'?",
        "Answer": "Guns 'n' Roses"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band's first single was 'Running Free' in 1980?",
        "Answer": "Iron Maiden"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the lead singer with the pop group Madness?",
        "Answer": "Suggs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one in 1995 with 'Cotton Eye Joe'?",
        "Answer": "Rednex"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the title of the French National Anthem?",
        "Answer": "La Marseillaise"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, how is James Jewel Osterberg better known?",
        "Answer": "Iggy Pop"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is Brian Warner better known as in the music world?",
        "Answer": "Marilyn Manson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1990 with the song 'Killer'?",
        "Answer": "Adamski"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following operas was not composed by Verdi? Aida, Carmen or La Traviata?",
        "Answer": "Carmen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit in 1984 with 'Hello'?",
        "Answer": "Lionel Richie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band got their name from a sexual device depicted in the book 'The Naked Lunch'?",
        "Answer": "Steely Dan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Britney Spears' first hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Baby One More Time'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1997, which song by D-Ream did the Labour Party adopt as the theme tune to their General Election campaign?",
        "Answer": "'Things Can Only Get Better'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer's 1988 concert in Rio broke the record for attendance with a crowd of almost 200,000?",
        "Answer": "Tina Turner's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single in the seventies with 'I Wish It Could Be Christmas Everyday'?",
        "Answer": "Wizzard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the four christian names of the members of the pop group ABBA?",
        "Answer": "Benny, Bjorn Agnetha and Annifred"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hit singles in the 80s called 'She Makes My Day' and 'I Didn't Mean To Turn You On'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Palmer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Everything we do is driven by you' was sung by Brian May of Queen in an advert for which car company?",
        "Answer": "Ford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'Benny' was known as the King of Swing?",
        "Answer": "Benny Goodman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following Simple Minds songs reached number 1 in the UK charts? 'Don't You Forget About Me', 'Alive And Kicking' or 'Belfast Child'?",
        "Answer": "'Belfast Child'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Duran Duran's first number one single in the UK charts?",
        "Answer": "'Is There Something I Should Know'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British band was named after Mr Spock's Vulcan friend from Star Trek?",
        "Answer": "T'Pau"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of drink lended itself to the title of a number one single for All Saints?",
        "Answer": "Black Coffee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous Chuck Berry song included the name of a classical composer in it's title?",
        "Answer": "'Roll Over Beethoven'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only single by the Spice Girls which didn't make it to number one?",
        "Answer": "'Stop'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal was Boris, who 'The Who' sang about?",
        "Answer": "A Spider"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Rank Her Fat Nail' is an anagram of which famous singer?",
        "Answer": "Aretha Franklin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the song, The Twelve Days of Christmas, what is the partridge in a pear tree said to symbolise?",
        "Answer": "Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Fats Waller was famous for playing which instrument?",
        "Answer": "Piano"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following operas was not composed by Mozart? Cosi Fan Tutti, Don Giovanni or La Boheme?",
        "Answer": "La Boheme"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer was born Robert Allen Zimmerman in 1941?",
        "Answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who did Ringo Starr replace in the Beatles?",
        "Answer": "Pete Best"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Travis song includes the line 'Is it because I lied when I was seventeen'?",
        "Answer": "Why Does It Always Rain On Me?"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Hairy Camera' is an anagram of which female singer?",
        "Answer": "Mariah Carey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released the album 'Dark Side of the Moon'?",
        "Answer": "Pink Floyd"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first singer to get 5 top ten hits from the same album?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson (from 'Thriller')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Geri Halliwell leave The Spice Girls?",
        "Answer": "1998"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was pianist and composer Franz Liszt?",
        "Answer": "Hungarian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which guitarist played the lead guitar solo on Michael Jackson's 'Beat It'?",
        "Answer": "Eddie Van Halen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one in 1974 called 'Seasons In The Sun'?",
        "Answer": "Terry Jacks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer had their only chart hit in 1991 with the theme to the Rugby World Cup?",
        "Answer": "Kiri Te Kawana"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2000, who became the first female to reach number one in the charts as a soloist, in a duo and as part of a group?",
        "Answer": "Melanie C"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song was a hit for both Freddie Mercury and The Platters?",
        "Answer": "'The Great Pretender'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had top ten hits in the 1990s with 'When Love And Hate Collide' and 'Let's Get Rocked'?",
        "Answer": "Def Leppard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many white keys are there on a standard piano?",
        "Answer": "52"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who recorded albums called 'Dangerous' and 'Bad'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had top ten hits in the UK in the 1990s with 'No, No, No' and 'Bills, Bills, Bills'?",
        "Answer": "Destiny's Child"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The video for which Queen song featured Freddie Mercury in stockings and a mini-skirt?",
        "Answer": "'I want to break free'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the pop-group All Saints' first UK hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Never Ever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had the bestselling album in the UK in 1999 called 'Come On Over'?",
        "Answer": "Shania Twain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Spandau Ballet's first single to reach number one in the UK charts?",
        "Answer": "'True'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who released an album called 'The Great Rock & Roll Swindle'?",
        "Answer": "The Sex Pistols"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British composer and playwright wrote the musical 'Oliver'?",
        "Answer": "Lionel Bart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Celine Dion won the Eurovision song contest for which European country?",
        "Answer": "Switzerland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who appeared in both the London & Philadelphia parts of the Live Aid Concerts?",
        "Answer": "Phil Collins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatle's album was the bestselling album in the 1960s in the UK?",
        "Answer": "'Sgt. Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In rock music, Marvin Lee Aday is better known by a high school nick-name. What is it?",
        "Answer": "Meatloaf"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Born in 1979, by what name is Alecia Moore better known as in the music world?",
        "Answer": "Pink"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the novelty song that Spitting Image took to number one in 1986?",
        "Answer": "'The Chicken Song'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which country do the band A-Ha come?",
        "Answer": "Norway"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Singer Alison Clarkson had hit records using what name?",
        "Answer": "Betty Boo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had a top 10 hit single in 1989 with 'Toy Soldiers'?",
        "Answer": "Martika"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous female singer appeared as a fairy in the 2001 film 'Moulin Rouge'?",
        "Answer": "Kylie Minogue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit in 1992 with 'I'm Doing Fine Now'?",
        "Answer": "The Pasadenas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'No Angel' is the debut album by which female singer?",
        "Answer": "Dido"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which rock star's autobiography is entitled 'I need more'?",
        "Answer": "Iggy Pop's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous song contains the line 'I met a girl who sang the blues, and I asked her for some happy news'?",
        "Answer": "'American Pie'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first DJ to be heard on Radio1?",
        "Answer": "Tony Blackburn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which country singer wrote the song 'I Will Always Love You' which was a hit for Whitney Houston in 1992?",
        "Answer": "Dolly Parton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Gwen Stefani is the lead singer with which band?",
        "Answer": "No Doubt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released the album 'Modern Life Is Rubbish'?",
        "Answer": "Blur"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who produced the early works by the band Genesis and was responsible for giving them their name?",
        "Answer": "Jonathan King"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had top ten hits in the 1960s with 'Don't Let Me Be Misunderstood' and 'We Gotta Get Out Of This Place'?",
        "Answer": "The Animals"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a hit album called 'Slippery When Wet'?",
        "Answer": "Bon Jovi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two singers had a hit with the duet 'Islands In The Stream' in 1983?",
        "Answer": "Dolly Parton and Kenny Rogers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Madonna song includes the line 'I have a taste for danger'?",
        "Answer": "'Beautiful Stranger'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band have had hits called 'Waiting For A Girl Like You' and 'I Want To Know What Love Is'?",
        "Answer": "Foreigner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is singer Paul Francis Gadd better known?",
        "Answer": "Gary Glitter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As in the music shop, what do the letters HMV stand for?",
        "Answer": "His Masters Voice"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a top ten hit in 2004 with 'Take Me Out'?",
        "Answer": "Franz Ferdinand"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Debbie Rowe became famous for marrying which music star?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who released albums called 'Slowhand', 'Behind The Sun' and 'August'?",
        "Answer": "Eric Clapton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the music world, how is Damon Gough better known?",
        "Answer": "Badly Drawn Boy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song reached number one for Tommy Roe in 1969 and then again in 1991 when covered by another band or artist?",
        "Answer": "'Dizzy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What girls name appears in the title of two David Bowie top ten singles - one in 1972 and one in 1984?",
        "Answer": "Jean ('The Jean Genie' and 'Blue Jean')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the youngest member of the Beatles?",
        "Answer": "George Harrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which trumpet player is said to have invented the word 'jazz'?",
        "Answer": "Louis Armstrong"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Oasis' first top ten hit in the UK?",
        "Answer": "'Live Forever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In February 2002, where in London were the Brit Awards held?",
        "Answer": "Earls Court"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song includes the line 'And I'm floating in the most peculiar way'?",
        "Answer": "'Space Oddity' by David Bowie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The English band Radiohead took there name from a song by which other band?",
        "Answer": "Talking Heads"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer formed Vinegar Joe in 1971, joined The Power Station in 1985 and also had success as a solo artist?",
        "Answer": "Robert Palmer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1980s, what drink was Michael Jackson advertising when he was almost killed?",
        "Answer": "Pepsi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer was the biggest selling female artist in America in the 1990s?",
        "Answer": "Mariah Carey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality is singer LeAnn Rimes?",
        "Answer": "American"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the hit single on which Frank and Nancy Sinatra duetted in 1967?",
        "Answer": "'Something Stupid'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which well known pop star's real surname is Gudmundsdottir?",
        "Answer": "Bjork's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous singer was originally cast in the 1968 film 'Chitty Chitty Bang Bang', but eventually cut out because the film's makers objected to the think bandage on his head covering a cyst?",
        "Answer": "Phil Collins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The soundtrack to which film was the best selling album in the UK in 1978?",
        "Answer": "'Saturday Night Fever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was the composer Chopin?",
        "Answer": "Polish"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the song 'Mr Tambourine Man' which was a hit for the band The Byrds?",
        "Answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a hit album called 'Ghost in the Machine'?",
        "Answer": "The Police"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose 1994 debut single was called 'Supersonic'?",
        "Answer": "Oasis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1994 with 'Zombie'?",
        "Answer": "The Cranberries"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer sang 'Better The Devil You Know' in the 1983 Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "Sonia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The song 'New York, New York' is from which Leonard Bernstein musical?",
        "Answer": "'On The Town'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which band was David Lee Roth lead vocalist in the 1980s?",
        "Answer": "Van Halen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'brothers' had a number one hit in May 1958 with 'All I Have To Do Is Dream'?",
        "Answer": "The Everly Brothers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What Beatles song was adapted to give the band Candy Flip a hit in 1990?",
        "Answer": "'Strawberry Fields Forever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang for both 'The Jam' and 'The Style Council'?",
        "Answer": "Paul Weller"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit with 'Everything I Own' in 1974?",
        "Answer": "Ken Boothe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Deacon Blue got their name from a song by which other band?",
        "Answer": "Steely Dan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit single in 2002 with 'Round Round'?",
        "Answer": "Sugarbabes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit with 'More Than Words' in 1991?",
        "Answer": "Extreme"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What famous song begins 'What'll you do when you get lonely, and nobody's waiting by your side'?",
        "Answer": "'Layla' (by Eric Clapton)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop star filed for divorce from her husband Cris Judd in July, 2002?",
        "Answer": "Jennifer Lopez"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who became the first African American to win the best actor award, when he did so at the 1964 Oscars?",
        "Answer": "Sidney Poitier"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American state was Elvis Presley born?",
        "Answer": "Mississippi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Take That's first number one single?",
        "Answer": "Pray"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1988 with 'My Perogative'?",
        "Answer": "Bobby Brown"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Royksopp, who released their debut album 'Melody AM' in 2002 are from which European country?",
        "Answer": "Norway"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which rock star took the photo which features on the front cover of Iggy Pop's album 'The Idiot'?",
        "Answer": "David Bowie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1991 with 'Move Any Mountain'?",
        "Answer": "The Shamen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the common age of Jimi Hendrix, Janis Joplin and Jim Morrison when they died?",
        "Answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop star played Adrian Mole's mother on TV?",
        "Answer": "Lulu"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Kelly Rowland, Michelle Williams and Beyonce Knowles make up which band?",
        "Answer": "Destiny's Child"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Johnny Rotten's real name?",
        "Answer": "John Lydon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of George Harrison's 1987 hit single which reached number 2 in the UK charts?",
        "Answer": "'Got My Mind Set On You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who came second in the Eurovision song contest for Britain in 1972 with the song 'Beg, Steal Or Borrow'?",
        "Answer": "The New Seekers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group, who had a number one hit in 1986, was fronted by singer Terri Nunn?",
        "Answer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1985 with the single 'Love and Pride'?",
        "Answer": "King"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Andrew Lloyd Webber wrote the music to which Boyzone song?",
        "Answer": "'No Matter What'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Oscar winner was born with the name Cherilyn La Pierre?",
        "Answer": "Cher"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the opera Tosca?",
        "Answer": "Puccini"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group got its name from a US spy plane?",
        "Answer": "U2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at January 2001, what has been the most aired video in  MTV's history?",
        "Answer": "'Sledgehammer' by Peter Gabriel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Oasis song includes the line 'I know I think I recognise your face, but I haven't seen you before'?",
        "Answer": "Roll With It"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the Beach Boys' first single to reach the UK top 40 singles chart?",
        "Answer": "'Surfin' USA'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the connection between the number one hit singles 'Come Outside' (1962), 'Every Loser Wins' (1986) and 'Perfect Moment' (1999)?",
        "Answer": "All recorded by actors or actresses who have appeared in 'Eastenders'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Eurovision song contest winner completed the 1981 Labour Party slogan 'The Tories have a worse record than ...'?",
        "Answer": "Bucks Fizz"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is singer songwriter Roberta Joan Anderson better known?",
        "Answer": "Joni Mitchell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Tori Amos song was remixed by Armand Van Helden for a hit single in 1997?",
        "Answer": "'Professional Widow'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Elvis Presley's first UK hit?",
        "Answer": "'Heartbreak Hotel'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Kate Bush's first number one single in the UK charts?",
        "Answer": "'Wuthering Heights'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit with 'Ride On Time' in 1989?",
        "Answer": "Black Box"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, which superstar was jailed in Tokyo in 1980 for drugs possession?",
        "Answer": "Paul McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which jazz musician had the nickname 'Bird'?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Parker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer sang with Take That on the hit song 'Relight My Fire'?",
        "Answer": "Lulu"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer's only UK top ten hit was called 'Good Tradition'?",
        "Answer": "Tanita Tikaram"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer's only UK top ten hit was called 'Good Tradition'?",
        "Answer": "Tanita Tikaram"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Sting's real name?",
        "Answer": "Gordon Sumner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single with 'The Only Way Is Up' in 1988?",
        "Answer": "Yazz and the Plastic Population"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whitney Houston's husband Bobby Brown was originally a member of which successful band?",
        "Answer": "New Edition"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1990, which Irish singer became the first artist to refuse a Grammy award?",
        "Answer": "Sinead O'Connor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was the 2003 Eurovision song contest be held?",
        "Answer": "Latvia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Cliff Richard sang which song in the 1968 Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "'Congratulations'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many symphonies did Beethoven write?",
        "Answer": "Nine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the song 'White Christmas'?",
        "Answer": "Irving Berlin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous singer had a twin brother called Jesse who died at birth?",
        "Answer": "Elvis Presley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Oasis' first number one UK hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Some Might Say'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Madonna's real first name?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song starts with the line 'I was happy in the haze of a drunken hour'?",
        "Answer": "'Heaven Knows I'm Miserable Know' by The Smiths"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the opera 'The Barber Of Seville'?",
        "Answer": "Rossini"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Steinway and Bosendorfer are all famous for making which musical instruments?",
        "Answer": "Pianos"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer was born Eilleen Regina Edwards?",
        "Answer": "Shania Twain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following composers has appeared in the title of a hit song for Chuck Berry? Mozart, Handel or Beethoven?",
        "Answer": "Beethoven ('Roll Over Beethoven')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980s song includes the line 'Please, Louise, pull me off'a my knees'?",
        "Answer": "'Footloose' (by Kenny Loggins)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which songwriter wrote the scores for the musicals 'Kiss Me Kate' and 'High Society'?",
        "Answer": "Cole Porter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2002, who filed for divorce from his wife Lisa Marie Presley after being married for just three months?",
        "Answer": "Nicolas Cage"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1969, what became the first song to be sung in outer space?",
        "Answer": "'Happy Birthday'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American band had a UK number one hit in 1990 with 'Hangin' Tough'?",
        "Answer": "New Kids On The Block"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Wham's first UK number one single?",
        "Answer": "'Wake me up before you go-go'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which feamle singer had a top ten hit with 'Bad Girl' in 1993?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the band The Animals' only UK number one hit single?",
        "Answer": "'House Of The Rising Sun'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which instrument does the leader of an orchestra play?",
        "Answer": "Violin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British female solo singer has the middle names Florian Cloud De Bounevialle?",
        "Answer": "Dido"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Sonia's song for Britain in the 1993 Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "Better The Devil You Know"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which boxer had a minor hit single in 1995 with 'Eye of the Tiger'?",
        "Answer": "Frank Bruno"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one in the UK singles chart in 1992 with a song called 'Stay'?",
        "Answer": "Shakespear's Sister"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Blondie's first UK number one hit single?",
        "Answer": "'Heart Of Glass'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group's last top ten hit single was called 'All Hooked Up' before they announced a split in 2001?",
        "Answer": "All Saints"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the opera 'Don Giovanni'? Mozart, Beethoven or Verdi?",
        "Answer": "Mozart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer married model Christie Brinkley in 1985?",
        "Answer": "Billy Joel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group sang with Elton John on the 2002 single 'Sorry Seems To Be The Hardest Word'?",
        "Answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Britains entry in the Eurovision Song Contest in 1976 with the song 'Save All Your Kisses For Me'?",
        "Answer": "Brotherhood Of Man"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer turned actor was born Terry Nelhams?",
        "Answer": "Adam Faith"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which three piece band were Ginger Baker and Jack Bruce members of?",
        "Answer": "Cream"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What position did 'Congratulations' by Cliff Richard come in the 1968 Eurovision Song Contest? 1st, 2nd or 13th?",
        "Answer": "2nd"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the nickname of the first Spice Girl to go solo?",
        "Answer": "Ginger Spice"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What became Hot Chocolate's first UK number one single in 1977? 'Everyone's A Winner', 'So You Win Again' or 'You Sexy Thing'?",
        "Answer": "'So You Win Again'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the nationality of the inventor of the piano?",
        "Answer": "Italian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When the band Hear'say formed, who was the oldest member at 24?",
        "Answer": "Kym"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was the composer Handel?",
        "Answer": "German."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name was James Marshall known in the music world?",
        "Answer": "Jimi Hendrix"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the 80s band of which Fatboy Slim was a member?",
        "Answer": "The Housemartins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, how many semi-quavers are in a crotchet?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the only two musical notes which have no flats?",
        "Answer": "C and F"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the words to Frank Sinatra's hit 'My way'?",
        "Answer": "Paul Anka"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'The Trolley Song', 'Under the Bamboo Tree' and 'Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas' are songs featured in which classic musical?",
        "Answer": "'Meet me in St Louis'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the opera 'Prince Igor'? Borodin, Offenbach or Weill?",
        "Answer": "Borodin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical instrument was also known as a clavier during the 18th century?",
        "Answer": "Harpsichord"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which two performers has Elton John recorded the duet 'Don't Go Breaking My Heart'?",
        "Answer": "Kiki Dee and Ru Paul"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hits with 'Hot In The City' and 'White Wedding'?",
        "Answer": "Billy Idol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit with 'Vindaloo' in 1998?",
        "Answer": "Fat Les"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Michael Jackson song was a UK Christmas number one in 1995?",
        "Answer": "'Earth Song'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two singers duetted on the 1991 UK number one hit single 'Don't Let The Sun Go Down On Me'?",
        "Answer": "George Michael and Elton John"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer published his autobiography called 'X-Ray' in 1995?",
        "Answer": "Ray Davies (of the Kinks)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American female singer fronted the 1970s rock band Blue Angel, before going on to solo success?",
        "Answer": "Cyndi Lauper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With what name did Johann Holzel have several hit records in the eighties?",
        "Answer": "Falco"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Ray Manzarek was the keyboard player with which American band?",
        "Answer": "The Doors"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Boyzone had a hit with which Cat Stevens song?",
        "Answer": "'Father And Son'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which song does the lyric 'Picture yourself in a boat on a river with tangerine trees and marmalade skies' come?",
        "Answer": "'Lucy in the sky with diamonds' (by The Beatles)."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical features the song 'I could have danced all night'?",
        "Answer": "'My Fair Lady'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singing duo were originally called Tom and Jerry?",
        "Answer": "Simon and Garfunkel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band finished 7th with the song 'Mary Ann' for the UK in the 1979 Eurovision song contest, before later going on to have a massive party hit in the UK several years later?",
        "Answer": "Black Lace"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous singer is an anagram of 'So Check Jail Man'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality is opera singer Placido Domingo?",
        "Answer": "Spanish"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which day of the year was the song 'Jingle Bells' originally written for? New Years Day, Boxing Day or Thanksgiving?",
        "Answer": "Thanksgiving"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had hits with 'I Am What I Am' and 'Never Can Say Goodbye'?",
        "Answer": "Gloria Gaynor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which ageing rock star won three Grammy awards in 1998, including one for his album 'Time Out Of Mind'?",
        "Answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Britney Spears song includes the line 'I must confess I still believe'?",
        "Answer": "Baby One More Time"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Lisa Scott Lee was a member of which British pop group?",
        "Answer": "Steps"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released the 1999 comeback single 'Maria'?",
        "Answer": "Blondie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor featured in the title of a Madness hit in 1984?",
        "Answer": "Michael Caine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to Elvis Presley, where was Heartbreak Hotel situated?",
        "Answer": "At the end of lonely street"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to the song 'The Twelve Days of Christmas', how many gifts in total did my true love give to me?",
        "Answer": "364"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band peform the theme tune to the TV show 'Friends'?",
        "Answer": "The Rembrandts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two singers duetted on the 1991 song 'Well Did You Ever'?",
        "Answer": "Iggy Pop and Debbie Harry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had the bestselling album in the UK in 1981 with 'Kings Of The Wild Frontier'?",
        "Answer": "Adam And The Ants"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one album in 2002 called 'Escapology'?",
        "Answer": "Robbie Williams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many strings are there on a normal a bass guitar?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was Whigfield who had a number one hit in 1994 with 'Saturday Night'?",
        "Answer": "Danish"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which Edith Piaf song did Grace Jones have a hit in 1986?",
        "Answer": "'La Vie En Rose'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is singer Georgios Kyriacos Panayiotou better known?",
        "Answer": "George Michael"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the title of a 1996 hit single The Divine Comedy was 'Becoming More Like ÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬ÃÂ¦' who?",
        "Answer": "Alfie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Kylie Minogue's debut album?",
        "Answer": "'Kylie'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a number one hit with 'Barbie Girl'?",
        "Answer": "Aqua"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatles song has been recorded the most by other artists?",
        "Answer": "'Yesterday'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was A-Ha's first number one single in the UK?",
        "Answer": "The Sun Always Shines On TV"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of No Doubt's hit single which included the line 'Don't tell me cos it hurts'?",
        "Answer": "'Don't speak'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Elvis die?",
        "Answer": "1977"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Madonna song includes the line 'I have a taste for danger'?",
        "Answer": "Beautiful Stranger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Radio 1 DJ announced he was leaving the station in August 2002, after 15 years?",
        "Answer": "Mark Goodier"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a UK number one hit single with 'I'm A Believer' in 1967?",
        "Answer": "The Monkees"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Geri Halliwell's single 'It's Raining Men' featured on the soundtrack to what film?",
        "Answer": "'Bridget Jones' Diary'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year was the first Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "1956"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Paul McCartney's middle name?",
        "Answer": "Paul"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Take That song includes the line 'Just tell me the song and I'll sing it'?",
        "Answer": "Back For Good"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 90s song includes the line 'What a wicked thing to do, to make me dream of you'?",
        "Answer": "Wicked Game (by Chris Isaak)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the musical term for a note that equals half a crotchet?",
        "Answer": "A quaver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In July 1998, who became the youngest solo act to top the UK charts with a debut single?",
        "Answer": "Billie Piper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first female DJ on Radio 1?",
        "Answer": "Annie Nightingale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won a record 7 Grammy awards in 1984?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit in 1994 with 'Mmm mmm mmm mmm'?",
        "Answer": "Crash Test Dummies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1988 with 'The First Time'?",
        "Answer": "Robin Beck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How did the pop group Abba get their name?",
        "Answer": "By taking the first letter from each of the band members names."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2003, what did the pop group S Club Juniors change their name to?",
        "Answer": "S Club 8"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hits in the 80s with 'It Must Be Love', 'Wings Of A Dove' and 'Uncle Sam'?",
        "Answer": "Madness"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which wood is traditionally used to make the black keys of a piano?",
        "Answer": "Ebony"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Spinderella is the female DJ for what rap group?",
        "Answer": "Salt-n-pepa"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American rock star was the first music artist to release a music album on CD?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Springsteen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What football team does singer Robbie Williams support?",
        "Answer": "Port Vale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Blondie song includes the line 'Go insane and out of your mind'?",
        "Answer": "Maria"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British band released an album called 'Treasure' on which all the song titles contain one word only?",
        "Answer": "The Cocteau Twins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song was a UK number 2 hit for both Nat King Cole and Rick Astley?",
        "Answer": "'When I Fall In Love'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "John Travolta and Olivia Newton John had UK number one hit singles in 1978 with which two songs?",
        "Answer": "'You're The One That I Want' and 'Summer Nights'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous model tried to embark on a career in music when she released the single 'Oh Yeah' in 1999?",
        "Answer": "Caprice"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Elvis Presley born?",
        "Answer": "1935"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What American singer released a 1999 album with a title 90 words long?",
        "Answer": "Fiona Apple ('When the pawn hits the conflicts...')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common title of hit singles for 'David Bowie', 'Five' and 'Chris Rea'?",
        "Answer": "'Let's Dance'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which member of the Beatles was the first to have a Number One hit after their break-up?",
        "Answer": "George Harrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the music world, which front man died of heart failure at the age of 27 in 1971?",
        "Answer": "Jim Morrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which All Saints song includes the line 'My head's spinning, boy I'm in a daze'?",
        "Answer": "Never Ever"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Jimi Hendrix's first single to reach the UK top 40 called?",
        "Answer": "'Hey Joe'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British band has had members called 3D, Daddy G and Mushroom?",
        "Answer": "Massive Attack"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were the first band to have a number one hit single with the word 'drugs' in it?",
        "Answer": "The Verve ('The Drugs Don't Work')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at January 2001, who is the only artist to have performed three James Bond title themes?",
        "Answer": "Shirley Bassey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which famous rock band did John Paul Jones play guitar?",
        "Answer": "Led Zeppelin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What condition did Karen Carpenter suffer from which eventually lead to her death?",
        "Answer": "Of anorexia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the Beatles' first UK number one single?",
        "Answer": "'From Me To You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The songs 'Aquarius', 'Good Morning Starshine' and 'Let The Sunshine In' are associated with what musical?",
        "Answer": "'Hair'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a hit first with 'Sweets for My Sweet'?",
        "Answer": "The Searchers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 70s pop group was fronted by Brian Connolly?",
        "Answer": "The Sweet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at 2004, who is the most successful female chart act of all time in the UK?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Neil Hannon had 9 top 40 singles in the 1990s under what name?",
        "Answer": "The Divine Comedy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which John Lennon song did Roxy Music take to number one the year after his death?",
        "Answer": "'Jealous Guy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How was pop star Priscilla Maria Veronica White better known?",
        "Answer": "Cilla Black"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who featured on Chicane's number one hit 'Don't Give Up'? Danii Minogue, Bryan Adams or Iggy Pop?",
        "Answer": "Bryan Adams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the late 1960s two bands called 'The Garden Wall' and 'The Anon' joined together to form which band?",
        "Answer": "Genesis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2001, which pop group turned on the Christmas lights in Oxford Street in London?",
        "Answer": "S Club 7"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1987 with the single 'Tonight, Tonight, Tonight'?",
        "Answer": "Genesis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the song 'I Shot the Sheriff' which Eric Clapton had a hit single with?",
        "Answer": "Bob Marley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first Beatles number one on which neither John or Paul sang the lead vocal?",
        "Answer": "'Yellow Submarine' (sung by Ringo)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous singer is an anagram of 'No I Decline'?",
        "Answer": "Celine Dion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the Italian for 'mixed fruits', and is also the title of a famous song?",
        "Answer": "'Tutti Frutti'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2000, who stopped Victoria Beckham reaching number one in the singles chart with her first non-Spice Girls single?",
        "Answer": "Spiller"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the lead singer with the American band 'The Go-Go's'?",
        "Answer": "Belinda Carlisle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit album in 1994 called 'Monster'?",
        "Answer": "R.E.M."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which British city were the rock group Def Leppard formed?",
        "Answer": "Sheffield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who's first solo album was released in 1979 and called 'The Pleasure Principle'?",
        "Answer": "Gary Numan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had the first chart hit (apart from the Beatles) with a Lennon-McCartney hit and what was the song?",
        "Answer": "Del Shannon ('From Me to You')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was David Bowie's first top ten hit single and later became his first number one when it was re-released 6 years later?",
        "Answer": "'Space Oddity'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Beatles' last live performance was at Candlestick Park in San Francisco. In what year was this?",
        "Answer": "1966"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2002, which actress/singer released the album 'This Is Me Then'?",
        "Answer": "Jennifer Lopez"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At the 2002 'Top Of The Pops' awards, which singer won the best tour award for her 'Fever' tour?",
        "Answer": "Kylie Minogue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang 'One Step Out Of Time' in the 1992 Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "Michael Ball"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the music world, how is Norman Cook better known?",
        "Answer": "Fatboy Slim"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'B. H.' first reached number one with a song called 'It Doesn't Matter Anymore'?",
        "Answer": "It Doesn't Matter Anymore"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Elton John song 'Empty Garden' was a tribute to who?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Abba song includes the line 'Do you still recall that fateful night we crossed the Rio Grande'?",
        "Answer": "Fernando"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which pop duo would you associate Theresa Bazaar and David Van Day?",
        "Answer": "Dollar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song begins 'When you're weary, feeling small; when tears are in your eyes'?",
        "Answer": "'Bridge over troubled water' by Simon and Garfunkel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which decade did The Faces have hits called 'Stay With Me' and 'Cindy Incidentally'?",
        "Answer": "1970s"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What father and daughter duo had a hit in 1967 with the song 'Something Stupid'?",
        "Answer": "Frank and Nancy Sinatra"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American band released their first mini-LP 'Chronic Town' in 1982?",
        "Answer": "R.E.M."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which male singer was backed by the 'Heartbreakers'?",
        "Answer": "Tom Petty"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What pop group got their name from a song by Bernard Cribbins?",
        "Answer": "Right Said Fred"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit single in the UK with 'Being With You' in 1981?",
        "Answer": "Smokey Robinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many keys are on a standard piano?",
        "Answer": "88"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which member of the band the Beatles wrote 'Here Comes The Sun'?",
        "Answer": "George Harrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the Beatles was the first to be a grandfather?",
        "Answer": "Ringo Starr"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two songs featured on the Beatles only single between 1963 and 1969 that failed to reach the top of the charts?",
        "Answer": "'Penny Lane' and 'Strawberry Fields Forever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do the songs 'Yellow Pearl' by Phil Lynott, 'Whole Lotta Love' by CCS and 'The Wizard' by Paul Hardcastle have in common?",
        "Answer": "They've all been used as theme tunes to 'Top Of The Pops'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group, who were founded in 1981 had members called Siobhan, Keren and Sarah?",
        "Answer": "Bananarama"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Robert Van Winkle was the real name of what American rapper?",
        "Answer": "Vanilla Ice"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hit singles in the 1990s including 'A Change Would Do You Good' and 'My Favourite Mistake'?",
        "Answer": "Sheyl Crow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the theme song for the Bond film 'Goldfinger'?",
        "Answer": "Shirley Bassey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Marmalades only number one hit in the UK?",
        "Answer": "'Ob-La-Di-Ob-La-Da'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released their third album called 'War' in 1983?",
        "Answer": "U2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Bryan Adams' first UK number one single?",
        "Answer": "'(Everything I Do) I Do It For You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a top ten hit in 1987 with '(Something Inside) So Strong'?",
        "Answer": "Labi Siffre"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the musical term da capo mean?",
        "Answer": "Repeat from the beginning"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at March 2003, who is the most successful female chart act of all time in the UK?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What classical composer wrote some of his greatest music after becoming deaf?",
        "Answer": "Beethoven"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who's piano was auctioned for 1.45 million pounds in October, 2000?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which instrument would you associate Caroline Corr?",
        "Answer": "Drums"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the only artist, as at November 2000,  to have had their first 10 singles reach the top 5 in the US charts?",
        "Answer": "Mariah Carey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Fun Lovin' Criminals' hit 'Love Unlimited' is a tribute to which singer?",
        "Answer": "Barry White"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Kurt Cobain commit suicide?",
        "Answer": "1994"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What song from the film 'Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid' won an Oscar for best song?",
        "Answer": "'Raindrops Keep Falling On My Head'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1999, who had her first UK number one with 'Genie In A Bottle'?",
        "Answer": "Christina Aguilera"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Kylie Minogue's first UK top 10 single?",
        "Answer": "'I should be so lucky'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the Bee Gees have a UK number one hit with 'Tragedy'?",
        "Answer": "1979"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The song 'Tomorrow' features in which musical?",
        "Answer": "'Annie'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had top ten hits in the 1980s with the singles 'Complex', 'We Are Glass' and 'She's Got Claws'?",
        "Answer": "Gary Numan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many of the Beatles' were left handed?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang 'Just A Little Bit', Britain's entry to the 1996 Eurovision Song Contest?",
        "Answer": "Gina G"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit album in 2002 called 'One Love'?",
        "Answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop star died three days before Groucho Marx?",
        "Answer": "Elvis Presley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which note do an orchestra normally tune to? A, C or G?",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in 1997 with 'Tubthumping'?",
        "Answer": "Chumbawumba"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the names of John Lennon's two sons?",
        "Answer": "Julian and Sean"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what city was John Lennon killed?",
        "Answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit in 1993 with the song 'Go West'?",
        "Answer": "The Pet Shop Boys"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Welsh band released the album 'The Holy Bible' in 1994?",
        "Answer": "Manic Street Preachers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What double act hold the record for the longest gap between number 1 records in the UK singles charts with hits in 1965 and 1990?",
        "Answer": "The Righteous Brothers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Guinness British Hit Singles book, who is listed as the most popular chart star of all time?",
        "Answer": "Elvis Presley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was composer Franz Schubert?",
        "Answer": "Austrian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer went solo after having success with the band the Commodores?",
        "Answer": "Lionel Richie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed the opera 'Turandot'? Wagner, Puccini or Verdi?",
        "Answer": "Puccini"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop group is an anagram of 'Pen Ballad At Us'?",
        "Answer": "Spandau Ballet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which male singer starred in a film version of the hit musical 'The Wiz' in 1977? Michael Jackson, Roger Daltrey or Meatloaf?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of song, written and performed by Harold Faltermeyer, on the soundtrack of the film 'Beverly Hills Cop'?",
        "Answer": "Axel F"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous singer was born Thomas Woodward in 1940?",
        "Answer": "Tom Jones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Stuart Sutcliffe of the Beatles died in 1962 of what cause?",
        "Answer": "Brain haemmoridge."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two singers dueted on the song 'Dancing In The Streets' in 1985?",
        "Answer": "David Bowie and Mick Jagger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two members of the Beatles didn't use their real first names?",
        "Answer": "Ringo Starr and Paul McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical composer wrote 'The Firebird', 'Petruska' and 'The Rite Of Spring'?",
        "Answer": "Stravinsky"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Britains entry in the Eurovision Song Contest in 1968 with the song 'Congratulations'?",
        "Answer": "Cliff Richard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The band Steely Dan got their name from a book by which American author?",
        "Answer": "William Burroughs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who released the 1968 album 'Two Virgins'?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon and Yoko Ono"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the last album ever recorded by the Beatles?",
        "Answer": "'Abbey Road'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Shut Up And Dance's top ten hit of 1992? 'Raving, I'm Raving' or 'The Bouncer'?",
        "Answer": "Raving, I'm Raving"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Oasis song includes the line 'I know I think I recognise your face, but I haven't seen you before'?",
        "Answer": "'Roll With It'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was 'Chain Reaction' a number one single for Diana Ross?",
        "Answer": "1986"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the first name of Julian Lennon's mother?",
        "Answer": "Cynthia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Simply Red song includes the line 'And I love the thought of coming home to you'?",
        "Answer": "Fairground"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1995, which singer was put on 18 months probation for firing a gun at two noisy teenagers? Ozzy Osbourne, Nina Simone or Van Morrison?",
        "Answer": "Nina Simone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer is famous for his 'moonwalk' dance?",
        "Answer": "Michael Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was the composer Beethoven?",
        "Answer": "German"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous rock star wrote the lines 'It's better to burn out than to fade away' in his suicide note?",
        "Answer": "Kurt Cobain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band did Nirvana's bass player Dave Grohl join after Nirvana split in 1995?",
        "Answer": "The Foo Fighters"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What song was the Christmas number one in the UK in both 1975 and 1991?",
        "Answer": "'Bohemian Rhapsody' by Queen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which song did Sacha Distel enter the UK charts 5 times?",
        "Answer": "'Raindrops Keep Falling On My Head'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer came third in the 1973 Eurovision Song Contest with the song 'Power To All Our Friends'?",
        "Answer": "Cliff Richard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Alvin Stardust had a number one in 1974 called 'Jealous ...' what?",
        "Answer": "Mind"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatle was the youngest? John, Paul, George or Ringo?",
        "Answer": "George"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress sang with Peter Sellers on the 1960 hit 'Goodness Gracious Me'?",
        "Answer": "Sophia Loren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did the Beatles officially split up?",
        "Answer": "1970"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released the album 'Second Coming' in 1994, five years after their debut album?",
        "Answer": "The Stone Roses"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 90s song includes the line 'What a wicked thing to do, to make me dream of you'?",
        "Answer": "'Wicked Game' (by Chris Isaak)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which of R.E.M.s albums would you find the songs 'Man On The Moon' and 'Everybody Hurts'?",
        "Answer": "Automatic For The People"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band reached number 2 in the UK charts in 1982 with the song 'Private Investigations'?",
        "Answer": "Dire Straits"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Madonna's maiden name?",
        "Answer": "Ciccone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had a number one hit with 'Mi Chico Latino'?",
        "Answer": "Geri Halliwell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatle's first girlfriend was called Thelma Pickles?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following groups were once called the Mugwumps? The Yardbirds, The Mamas And Papas or Mott The Hoople?",
        "Answer": "The Mamas And Papas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Colonel was the manager of Elvis Presely?",
        "Answer": "Tom Parker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the folk singer and ex-busker from Cleveland who filled in for Stevie Wonder at the 1988 UK Nelson Mandella Concert?",
        "Answer": "Tracey Chapman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which British Rock group did Ozzy Osbourne make his name?",
        "Answer": "Black Sabbath"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following rock stars worked as a gravedigger before starting his musical career? Rod Stewart, Freddie Mercury or Billy Joel?",
        "Answer": "Rod Stewart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which songwriting duo wrote 'You'll Never Walk Alone'?",
        "Answer": "Rogers and Hammerstein"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of David Bowie's 1977 album, his first of three collaborations with Brian Eno?",
        "Answer": "'Low'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In January 2003, it was reported that Dave Glover had been thrown out of which band due to his relationship with convicted murderer Rosemary West?",
        "Answer": "Slade"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many members were in the band All Saints?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Richard Starkey is the real name of which famous musician?",
        "Answer": "Ringo Starr"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won the 'Best International Male' award at the Brit awards of 2000?",
        "Answer": "Beck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the song, The Twelve Days of Christmas, what are the 10 Lords-a-leaping said to symbolise?",
        "Answer": "The Ten Commandments"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang with Craig McLachlan on the 1993 single 'You're The One That I Want'?",
        "Answer": "Debbie Gibson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous Christmas Carol, was originally written in 1857 for Thanksgiving?",
        "Answer": "'Jingle Bells'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Elvis Presley's daughter?",
        "Answer": "Lisa Marie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was George Michael's first solo UK single to reach the top 40?",
        "Answer": "'Careless Whisper'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a hit with a song called 'Rain' in 1975 and which female singer had a hit with a song of the same title in 1993?",
        "Answer": "Status Quo and Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose first UK top ten 20 single was 'Eyes Without A Face' in 1984?",
        "Answer": "Billy Idol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many cellos are involved in a typical string quartet?",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Talking Heads first UK top ten hit?",
        "Answer": "'Road To Nowhere'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Fatboy Slim's first UK number one single?",
        "Answer": "'Praise You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Before going solo, Lionel Richie sang with which group?",
        "Answer": "The Commodores"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which boy band released the 1999 album 'By Request'?",
        "Answer": "Boyzone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the common title of an Elvis Presley movie and a hit song for Motley Crue?",
        "Answer": "'Girls, Girls, Girls'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following musical notes does not exist? B sharp, C sharp or D sharp?",
        "Answer": "B sharp"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was The Divine Comedy's first top twenty hit?",
        "Answer": "Something For The Weekend"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many strings does a ukulele have? None, four or six?",
        "Answer": "Four"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous composer was known as the 'Waltz King'?",
        "Answer": "Johann Strauss"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which Bond movie did Matt Monroe sing the theme song?",
        "Answer": "'From Russia With Love'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band's 1997 debut album was called 'Good Feeling'?",
        "Answer": "Travis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit single in the 1980s with 'Pass The Dutchie'?",
        "Answer": "Musical Youth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatle's middle name is Winston?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Slave To The Vibe' was a top twenty hit in 1993 for which group which is also the name of an alcoholic drink?",
        "Answer": "Aftershock"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song includes the line 'Just tell me the song and I'll sing it' and which boy band had a hit with it in the nineties?",
        "Answer": "'Back For Good' by Take That"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who did singer Edie Brickell marry in 1992? Paul Simon, Bob Dylan or Bruce Springsteen?",
        "Answer": "Paul Simon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer was once married to Simple Minds singer Jim Kerr and had a child with Ray Davies of The Kinks?",
        "Answer": "Chrissie Hynde"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to the Pulp song 'Common People', 'she studied' what 'at St. Martin's college'?",
        "Answer": "Sculpture"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sings the theme tune to the TV game show 'Big Break'?",
        "Answer": "Captain Sensible"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit in 1998 with 'Frozen'?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two singers duetted on the 1987 hit 'I Knew You Were Waiting For Me'?",
        "Answer": "George Michael and Aretha Franklin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of the Beatles' first single?",
        "Answer": "'Love Me Do'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Scottish band had a hit album in 1999 with 'The Man Who'?",
        "Answer": "Travis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical composer wrote 'Hungarian Rhapsodies'?",
        "Answer": "Liszt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was backed by the Blackhearts in the early 1980s?",
        "Answer": "Joan Jett"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Using a pseudonym, who wrote the song 'Manic Monday' which was a hit for the Bangles?",
        "Answer": "Prince"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the lead singer with the pop group Altered Images?",
        "Answer": "Claire Grogan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What famous musical is also the name of an American state?",
        "Answer": "Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Your Song' in 1970 was the first American hit by which British artist?",
        "Answer": "Elton John"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group had a UK number one hit single in 1977 with 'So You Win Again'?",
        "Answer": "Hot Chocolate"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who duetted with Diana Ross on the hit single 'Endless Love'?",
        "Answer": "Lionel Richie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Tim Booth is the lead singer with which British band?",
        "Answer": "James"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the song 'Jealous Guy'?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the song 'the twelve days of christmas', what did my true love send to me on the 9th day?",
        "Answer": "9 ladies dancing"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whigfield, who had a hit single with 'Saturday Night', comes from which country?",
        "Answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of LuluÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s backing group?",
        "Answer": "Luvvers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Stealers Wheel song is playing in 'Reservoir Dogs' when Mr Blonde tortures a police officer?",
        "Answer": "'Stuck In The Middle With You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Victoria Beckham's maiden name?",
        "Answer": "Adams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the song 'My Darling Clementine' how did Clementine die?",
        "Answer": "Drowning"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer is known as the 'Belfast Cowboy'?",
        "Answer": "Van Morrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won the Eurovision song contest for Ireland singing 'What's Another Year'?",
        "Answer": "Johnny Logan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the title of Crowded House's only UK top ten hit?",
        "Answer": "'Weather With You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit album in 1973 with 'Don't Shoot Me, I'm Only The Piano Player'?",
        "Answer": "Elton John"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who's 1981 debut album was called 'Boy'?",
        "Answer": "U2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many operas did Beethoven write?",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What legendary rock star's real name was Johnny Allen?",
        "Answer": "Jimi Hendrix"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song includes the line 'My head's spinning, boy I'm in a daze'?",
        "Answer": "'Never Ever' (by All Saints)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American band had a top ten hit in 1976 called '26 Or 6 To 4'?",
        "Answer": "Chicago"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which single spent 16 weeks at number one in the UK music charts in 1991?",
        "Answer": "'Everything I Do I Do It For You' by Bryan Adams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Beethoven's only opera?",
        "Answer": "'Fidelio'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer recorded the 1993 album 'The Red Shoes'?",
        "Answer": "Kate Bush"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, which controversial star auctioned his Mustang car for almost $30,000 in July 2002?",
        "Answer": "Eminem"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many verses make up the national anthem 'God Save The Queen'?",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the nanny in the 1992 film 'The Hand That Rocks The Cradle'?",
        "Answer": "Rebecca De Mornay"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a top ten hit in 1986 called 'What's The Colour Of Money'?",
        "Answer": "Hollywood Beyond"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had the bestselling album in the UK in 1982 with 'Love Songs'?",
        "Answer": "Barbra Streisand"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous young pop star married Jason Alexander in Las Vegas in January 2004?",
        "Answer": "Britney Spears"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In April 2004, which 'Osbourne' entered drug rehabilitation clinic for addiction to painkillers?",
        "Answer": "Kelly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the song 'Who Wants to be a Millionaire'?",
        "Answer": "Cole Porter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At which British city was Gig In The Green held in 2002?",
        "Answer": "Glasgow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Queen song is generally regarded as the first to be hit sold on TV by it's video?",
        "Answer": "'Bohemian Rhapsody'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Sooner Or Later' and 'You Must Love Me' were Oscar winning songs performed by which singer?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who's debut album was called 'Left Of The Middle'?",
        "Answer": "Natalie Imbruglia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer's 1983 tour was called 'The Serious Moonlight Tour'?",
        "Answer": "David Bowie's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band has released albums called 'His n Hers' and 'Different Class'?",
        "Answer": "Pulp"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the Bee Gees are twins?",
        "Answer": "Maurice and Robin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer won the Eurovision Song Contest with 'A Little Peace' and what was her nationality?",
        "Answer": "Nicole - German"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Buggles 'Video Killed the Radio Star' was the first video to be shown on MTV. In what year was this?",
        "Answer": "1981"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 90s number one included the line 'You can brush me hair, undress me anywhere'?",
        "Answer": "Barbie Girl (by Aqua)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which member of The Beatles is pictured barefoot on the front cover of the Abbey Road album?",
        "Answer": "Paul McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous rock group were once called The High Numbers?",
        "Answer": "The Who"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'Ian' featured on the Madness song 'Drip Fed Fred'?",
        "Answer": "Ian Dury"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1986 film included the song 'Take My Breath Away' by Berlin?",
        "Answer": "'Top Gun'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose first hit single was 'What Have You Done For Me Lately' which reached number 3 in 1986?",
        "Answer": "Janet Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Bob Dylan song was taken to number 1 in the UK in 1965 by The Byrds?",
        "Answer": "'Mr Tambourine Man'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the song 'All Along The Watchtower', which was a hit for Jimi Hendrix?",
        "Answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Steve, Larry and Jimmy were the first names of which 80's pop group?",
        "Answer": "Bronski Beat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Elvis Presley song was based on the Italian folk song 'O Sole Mio'?",
        "Answer": "'It's Now Or Never'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In April 2004, which singer did Glastonbury organiser Michael Eavis demand an apology from?",
        "Answer": "Justin Hawkins (of The Darkness)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who released the album 'Wednesday Morning' in 1964?",
        "Answer": "Simon and Garfunkel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop song includes the lyrics 'Don't let your indecision take you from behind'?",
        "Answer": "'Making Your Mind Up' (by Bucks Fizz)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song by Jackie Wilson was originally released in 1957, and reached number one in the UK when re-issued in 1986?",
        "Answer": "'Reet Petite'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the 90s song which includes the line 'I swear I left her by the river' and who had a hit with it?",
        "Answer": "'Hazard' by Richard Marx"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatles single gave its name to the John Lennon memorial garden in Central Park?",
        "Answer": "'Strawberry Fields Forever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What band provided the music for the musical 'Tommy'?",
        "Answer": "The Who"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the oldest member of U2?",
        "Answer": "Adam Clayton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer teamed up with the KLF for their hit 'Justified and Ancient'?",
        "Answer": "Tammy Wynette"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which folk opera, in which all the cast were black, did George Gershwin write the music for?",
        "Answer": "''Porgy and Bess'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who has had hit albums called 'Mutations' and 'Midnite Vultures'?",
        "Answer": "Beck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Guns 'n' Roses had a hit with a cover version of which James Bond theme tune?",
        "Answer": "'Live And Let Die'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is Graham McPherson better known as in the music world?",
        "Answer": "Suggs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous Scandanavian pop group got their name by the members taking the first letter of each of their names?",
        "Answer": "Abba"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 90's song includes the line 'Take a deep breath and get real high'?",
        "Answer": "What's Up (by 4 Non-Blondes)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Spice Girl released a solo album called 'A Girl Like Me'?",
        "Answer": "Emma Bunton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the world's most popular musical instrument? Harmonica, Flute or Acoustic Guitar?",
        "Answer": "Harmonica"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the band Steps, one member is nicknamed 'H'. What word does this letter stand for?",
        "Answer": "Hyperactive"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had top ten hits in the 1990s with 'Goldfinger' and 'Oh yeah'?",
        "Answer": "Ash"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, how is Harry Webb better known?",
        "Answer": "Cliff Richard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1974 number one with just one three letter word in the title was the the theme from the TV series 'The Seven Faces Of Woman'?",
        "Answer": "She"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Sheffield band made the Top 10 twice with their hit single 'Temptation'?",
        "Answer": "Heaven 17"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 2 Queen albums were named after Marx Brothers films?",
        "Answer": "A Night at the Opera, A Day at the Races"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a top ten hit in 1998 called 'I Don't Want To Miss A Thing'?",
        "Answer": "Aerosmith"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had top ten hits in the 1990s with 'No Son Of Mine' and 'I Can't Dance'?",
        "Answer": "Genesis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who duetted with Michael Jackson on 'The Girl Is Mine'?",
        "Answer": "Paul McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following bands were once called the Warlocks? AC/DC, The Grateful Dead or Talking Heads?",
        "Answer": "The Grateful Dead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the runner-up in ITV's 'Pop Idol' competition in 2002?",
        "Answer": "Gareth Gates"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Roachford's biggest hit single in the UK?",
        "Answer": "Cuddly Toy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number 2 hit in 1979 with 'Pop Muzik'?",
        "Answer": "M"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who released the album 'The Joshua Tree' in 1987?",
        "Answer": "U2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American state was Madonna born?",
        "Answer": "Michigan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit in 1986 with 'Nothing's gonna change my love for you'?",
        "Answer": "Glenn Medeiros"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal was Boris, who the rock group 'The Who' sang about?",
        "Answer": "Spider"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Janis Joplin die?",
        "Answer": "1970"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical does the song 'I know him so well' come from?",
        "Answer": "'Chess'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Paul Hewson and Dave Evans are the real names of members of which rock band?",
        "Answer": "U2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is popstar Darius' surname?",
        "Answer": "Danesh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which D. G. is credited as having discovered the singer Kate Bush?",
        "Answer": "Dave Gilmour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The band 'M People' come from which English city?",
        "Answer": "Manchester"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'When Will I See You Again' was a number one hit in 1974 for which group?",
        "Answer": "The Three Degrees"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Jimi Hendrix's only UK number 1 single?",
        "Answer": "'Voodoo Chile'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had hits in the 80s with 'Live To Tell', 'Causing A Commotion' and 'Express Yourself'?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where in England was the rock guitarist Slash from Guns 'n' Roses born? Grimsby, Hartlepool or Stoke on Trent?",
        "Answer": "Stoke on Trent"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality are the rock groups the Stereophonics and Catatonia?",
        "Answer": "Welsh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1980, who became the first British solo female artist to have a UK number one album?",
        "Answer": "Kate Bush"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Slade first have a hit with the song 'Merry Christmas Everybody'? 1973, 1975 or 1977?",
        "Answer": "1973"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who gave the Beatles their name in April 1960? Paul McCartney, John Lennon or Stuart Sutcliffe?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Robbie Williams first solo top ten single called?",
        "Answer": "'Freedom'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous song contains the line 'I feel stupid and contagious'?",
        "Answer": "'Smells Like Teen Spirit' (by Nirvana)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following artists came highest in the Eurovision Song Contest for Britain in the 1990s? Michael Ball, Gina G or Love City Groove?",
        "Answer": "Michael Ball"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Tony Orlando was the lead singer with which band?",
        "Answer": "Dawn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous female singer made her movie debut alongside Tupac Shakur in the film 'Poetic Justice'?",
        "Answer": "Janet Jackson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous song contains the line 'I feel stupid and contagious'?",
        "Answer": "Smells Like Teen Spirit"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed 'The Four Seasons'?",
        "Answer": "Vivaldi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had top ten hits in the nineties with 'End Of The Line', 'Love Of A Lifetime' and 'Never Let You Down'?",
        "Answer": "The Honeyz"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who narrates the initial lines in the Pink Floyd song 'Keep Talking'?",
        "Answer": "Stephen Hawking"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the oldest member of the Beatles?",
        "Answer": "Ringo Starr"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which DJ runs the record label Perfecto?",
        "Answer": "Paul Oakenfold"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following is not one of Michael Jackson's brothers? Joe, Marlon or Tito?",
        "Answer": "Joe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following operas was first performed before the other two? The Merry Widow, Carmen or Madame Butterfly?",
        "Answer": "Carmen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a hit in the nineties with the song 'Breakfast At Tiffany's'?",
        "Answer": "Deep Blue Something"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Madness song starts with the line 'Good morning miss, can I help you son'?",
        "Answer": "'House Of Fun'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one in 1974 called 'Always Yours'? Suzi Quattro, Gary Glitter or Pilot?",
        "Answer": "Gary Glitter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which adult male singing voice is lower than tenor but higher than bass?",
        "Answer": "Baritone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, Pulp, Def Leppard and ABC all come from which English city?",
        "Answer": "Sheffield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band did singer Louise leave to go solo?",
        "Answer": "Eternal"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What single by 'Wet Wet Wet' spent 15 weeks at number one in the UK charts in 1994?",
        "Answer": "Love Is All Around"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the first names of the Everly Brothers?",
        "Answer": "Don and Phil"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Texas song includes the line 'You can tell me your reasons, but it won't change my feelings'?",
        "Answer": "Say What You Want"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 80s pop star wrote Chesney Hawke's hit single 'The One & Only'?",
        "Answer": "Nik Kershaw"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the Beautiful South's first UK top 40 single?",
        "Answer": "'Song For Whoever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one hit in May 1958 with 'All I Have To Do Is Dream'?",
        "Answer": "Everly Brothers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Thunderbirds Are Go' was a top ten hit in 1990 for FAB featuring who?",
        "Answer": "MC Parker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a Top 10 hit in 1969 with 'Pictures of Lily'?",
        "Answer": "The Who"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the musical term 'adagio' mean?",
        "Answer": "Slow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two singers duetted on the 1981 hit 'Endless Love'?",
        "Answer": "Lionel Richie and Diana Ross"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In music, how many UK number ones has Ken Dodd had?",
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What Welsh band were originally known as 'Betty Blue'?",
        "Answer": "Manic Street Preachers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played lead guitar for Pink Floyd?",
        "Answer": "Dave Gilmour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical term means 'notes of a chord played in quick succession'?",
        "Answer": "Arpeggio"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatle was part of the Travelling Wilburys?",
        "Answer": "George Harrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Welsh band had the first UK number one of the 21st century?",
        "Answer": "Manic Street Preachers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The song 'Good Morning To All' written by the sisters Mildred and Patty Hill, was later adapted by Robert Coleman to become which famous song?",
        "Answer": "'Happy Birthday To You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the initial 'P' stand for in the singer P. J. Harvey's name?",
        "Answer": "Polly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What instrument did Dave Clarke play in the Dave Clarke Five?",
        "Answer": "Drums"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What instrument was Louis Armstrong most famous for playing?",
        "Answer": "Trumpet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song from the 80s includes the line 'Before this river becomes an ocean'?",
        "Answer": "'Faith' by George Michael"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the lead singer of the 1960s Irish group, 'Them'?",
        "Answer": "Van Morrisson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the manager of the punk band  'The Sex Pistols'?",
        "Answer": "Malcolm McLaren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who's was the first voice on the original Band Aid single 'Do They Know It's Christmas'?",
        "Answer": "Paul Young's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer had a 1990 hit album called 'The Immaculate Collection'?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was John Lennon's original middle name and what did he change it to before he died?",
        "Answer": "Originally 'Winston', but changed to 'Ono'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality were the band the Chi-Lites? British, American or Canadian?",
        "Answer": "American"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which song includes the line 'Mere alcohol doesn't thrill me at all'?",
        "Answer": "I Get A Kick Out Of You"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American band had a hit single in the year 2000 with 'The Great Beyond'?",
        "Answer": "R.E.M."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Snot Rap' was a 1983 top 10 hit single for which TV personality?",
        "Answer": "Kenny Everett"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Elvis Presley's middle name?",
        "Answer": "Aaron"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which band would you associate Jack and Meg White?",
        "Answer": "The White Stripes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Wichita Lineman' was the first British top ten hit for who?",
        "Answer": "Glen Campbell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer released her debut album 'Not That Kind' in the year 2000?",
        "Answer": "Anastacia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who did Stevie Wonder write the song 'Happy Birthday' for?",
        "Answer": "Martin Luther King"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which rock group had a hit with 'The Final Countdown'?",
        "Answer": "Europe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who composed 'Moonlight Sonata''? Handel, Mozart or Beethoven?",
        "Answer": "Beethoven"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Abba's first British hit single?",
        "Answer": "Waterloo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many UK number ones did Take That have in the 1990s?",
        "Answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two singers duetted on the 1982 hit single 'Ebony & Ivory'?",
        "Answer": "Paul McCartney and Stevie Wonder"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a number one with 'Little Things Mean A Lot' in 1954? Kitty Kallen, Jo Stafford or Vera Lynn?",
        "Answer": "Kitty Kallen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV actor provided the voice for Bob the Builder on his number one hit?",
        "Answer": "Neil Morrissey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band had a number one hit single called 'Star Trekkin'?",
        "Answer": "The Firm"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical style has a name which means 'in the style of the chapel' in Italian?",
        "Answer": "A Cappella (singing without instrumental accompaniment)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band provided the main theme song for the film 'Mission Impossible 2'?",
        "Answer": "Limp Bizkit"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Kurt Cobain commit suicide?",
        "Answer": "1994"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Beatles song was the biggest selling single in the UK in the 1960s?",
        "Answer": "'She Loves You'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'OK Computer', 'Pablo Honey' and 'Kid A' are all albums by which British band ?",
        "Answer": "Radiohead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had the 1981 hit single 'Good Year For the Roses'?",
        "Answer": "Elvis Costello"
    }
]